(Bernadette:)We need to save it.
(Howard:)Well, how do we do that?
(Bernadette:)Um, I don't know,
look it up on your phone.
I-I'm gonna wrap it in a towel.
Um... "taking care
of injured rabbit."
(Amy:)Okay.
(Howard:)Make sure
it's comfortable and warm.
(Howard:)Well, it was just in a hot tub.
I'm gonna say "check."
(Bernadette:)Anything else?
(Howard:)To make sure it's
not dehydrated,
(Howard:)feed him an
electrolyte solution.
(Howard:)If it's not responding,
(Howard:)use a warm cloth to wash
its face and genitals.
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(sighs)
This is ridiculous.
(Penny:)You know, I'm gonna
go talk to the maître d'.
(Leonard:)What are you gonna say?
(Bernadette:)I don't know.
I'm... I'm gonna flirt with him.
(Bernadette:)I don't know
if I'm comfortable with that.
(Raj:)I'm still
sleeping with you tonight.
(Leonard:)See if you can
get a table by the window.
(Penny:)Hi there.
What's your name?
(Maitre d':)Glen.
Oh, boy,
(Penny:)it is crazy in here
tonight, huh, Glen?